animaapp.com 2019-04-12

# 

                          TERMS OF SERVICE FOR ANIMA SERVICES
Introduction
1. Hello and welcome to AnimaApp.com. AnimaApp features a Mac app, a mobile
    app, plugins for design softwares and a web site (the "​AnimaApp​"). AnimaApp
    and the services offered via AnimaApp, is owned and operated by Anima App,
    Inc. registered in Delaware, US. (hereafter referred to as "​AnimaApp​" "​we​" or
    "​us​" or "​Company​").
2. AnimaApp offers you a set of tools for websites and mobile app design, including
    software for Mac, a mobile app, plugins for design softwares and websites.
3. By using our software, or visiting our website and accessing the information,
    resources, services, products, and tools we provide, you (hereafter referred to as
    "​you​" or "​Customer​" or ​“User” or ​“Visitor”​) understand and agree to accept and
    adhere to the following terms and conditions as stated in this policy (hereafter
    referred to as "​User Agreement"​ or "​Agreement​" or “​Terms of Service​”).
4. We reserve the right to change this User Agreement from time to time without
    notice. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this
    User Agreement periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. Your
    continued      use   of this site after such modifications will constitute
    acknowledgment and agreement of the modified terms and conditions.
You Represent and Warrant That
5. You are at least eighteen (18) years of age, or of the legal age of majority in your
    jurisdiction, and possess the legal authority, right and freedom to enter into the
    AnimaApp Terms and to form a binding agreement, for yourself or on behalf of
    the person or entity committed by you to the AnimaApp Terms.
6. You understand that AnimaApp does not provide any legal advice or any
    recommendation with respect to any laws or requirements applicable to your
    use or any of your End Users, or your compliance therewith.
                                              1

And Specifically Regarding Your User Content
7. You own all rights in and to any content uploaded by you (“User Content”),
    including any designs, images, code, animations, videos, audio files, fonts, logos,
    illustrations, compositions, artworks, interfaces, text, literary works and any
    other materials (“Content”), or otherwise have (and will continue to have) the
    full power, title, licenses, consents and authority, in and to the User Content, as
    necessary to legally use, publish, transfer or license any and all rights and
    interests in and to such User Content.
8. The User Content is (and will continue to be) true, current, accurate,
    non-infringing upon any third party rights. The User Content is not illegal, does
    not infringes on any trademark, patent, trade secret, or copyright, and in no way
    unlawful for you to possess, post, transmit or display in the country in which you
    or your User Website’s or applications visitors and users (“End Users”) reside, or
    for AnimaApp and/or your End Users to use or possess in connection with
    AnimaApp Services.
9. You have obtained all consents and permissions required under all applicable
    laws, regarding the posting, transmission and publication of any personal
    information and/or image or likeness of any person, entity or property which is
    part of the User Content, and you will adhere to all laws applicable thereto.
10. We have the right at our sole discretion to remove any content that, we feel in
    our judgment does not comply with this User Agreement, along with any content
    that we feel is otherwise harmful or violates any third party copyrights or
    trademarks. You hereby consent to such removal, and consent to waive any
    claim against us.
11. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless AnimaApp and its affiliates, and their
    directors, officers, managers and employees from and against all losses,
    expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting
    from any violation of this User Agreement or the failure to fulfill any obligations
    relating to your account incurred by you or any other person using your account.
    We reserve the right to take over the exclusive defense of any claim for which we
                                            2

    are entitled to indemnification under this User Agreement. In such event, you
    shall provide us with such cooperation as is reasonably requested by us.
Service Fees and Payments
12. The use of certain AnimaApp Services may be subject to payment of particular
    fees, as determined by AnimaApp in its sole discretion (“Paid Services” and
    “Fee(s)”, respectively). AnimaApp will provide notice of such Fees then in effect
    in relation to such Paid Services. If you wish to receive or use such Paid Services,
    you are required to pay all applicable Fees in advance.
13. AnimaApp reserves the right to change its Fees at any time, upon notice to you if
    such change may affect your existing subscriptions. If you received a discount or
    other promotional offer, AnimaApp shall have the right to automatically and
    without notice renew your subscription to such AnimaApp Service(s) at the full
    applicable Fee.
14. All Fees shall be deemed to be in U.S. Dollars, except as specifically stated
    otherwise in writing by AnimaApp. To the extent permitted by law (and unless
    specified otherwise by AnimaApp in writing), all Fees are exclusive of all taxes
    (including value added tax, sales tax, goods and services tax, etc.), levies or duties
    imposed by taxing authorities (“Taxes”), and you shall be responsible for
    payment of all applicable Taxes relating to your use of the AnimaApp Services, or
    to any payments or purchases made by you. If AnimaApp is obligated to collect
    or pay Taxes for the Fees payable by you, and whether or not such Taxes were
    added and collected from you for previous transactions, such Taxes may be
    added to the payment of any outstanding Fees and will be reflected in the
    Invoice for such transaction. We recommend that you verify the existence of any
    additional fees you may be charged by third parties in connection with the
    purchase of Paid Services or in connection with the renewal thereof (such as
    international transaction fees, currency exchange fees or fees due to banks or
    credit card companies). AnimaApp is not responsible for any such additional fees
    or costs.
                                            3

15. As part of registering or submitting information to receive Paid Services, you also
    authorize AnimaApp (either directly or through its affiliates, subsidiaries or other
    third parties) to request and collect payment (or otherwise charge, refund or
    take any other billing actions) from our payment provider or your designated
    banking account, and to make any inquiries AnimaApp or its affiliates may
    consider necessary to validate your designated payment account or financial
    information, in order to ensure prompt payment, including for the purpose of
    receiving updated payment details from your payment, credit card or banking
    account provider (e.g., updated expiry date or card number as may be provided
    to us by your credit card company).
Responsible Use and Conduct
16. By visiting our website and accessing/using the information, resources, services,
    products, and tools we provide for you (hereafter referred to as "​Resources​"),
    you agree to use these Resources only for the purposes intended as permitted by
    (a) the terms of this User Agreement, and (b) applicable laws, regulations and
    generally accepted online practices or guidelines.
    Wherein, you understand that:
17. In order to access our Resources, you may be required to provide certain
    information about yourself (such as identification, contact details, etc.) as part of
    the registration process, or as part of your ability to use the Resources. You agree
    that any information you provide will always be accurate, correct, and up to
    date.
18. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any login information
    associated with any account you use to access our Resources. Accordingly, you
    are responsible for all activities that occur under your account/s.
19. Accessing (or attempting to access) any of our Resources by any means other
    than through the means we provide, is strictly prohibited. You specifically agree
    not to access (or attempt to access) any of our Resources through any
    automated, unethical or unconventional means.
                                              4

20. Engaging in any activity that disrupts or interferes with our Resources, including
    the servers and/or networks to which our Resources are located or connected, is
    strictly prohibited.
21. Attempting to copy, duplicate, reproduce, sell, trade, or resell our Resources is
    strictly prohibited.
22. You are solely responsible for any consequences, losses, or damages that we may
    directly or indirectly incur or suffer due to any unauthorized activities conducted
    by you, as explained above, and may incur criminal or civil liability.
Confidentiality; Proprietary Rights
23. Each party (the “​Receiving Party​”) understands that the other party (the
    “​Disclosing Party​”) has disclosed or may disclose business, technical or financial
    information relating to the Disclosing Party’s business (hereinafter referred to as
    “​Proprietary Information​” of the Disclosing Party). Proprietary Information of
    AnimaApp includes non-public information regarding features, functionality and
    performance of the Service. Proprietary Information of Customer includes
    non-public data provided by Customer to Company to enable the provision of the
    Services (“​Customer Data​”). The Receiving Party agrees: (i) to take reasonable
    precautions to protect such Proprietary Information, and (ii) not to use (except in
    performance of the Services or as otherwise permitted herein) or divulge to any
    third person any such Proprietary Information. The Disclosing Party agrees that
    the foregoing shall not apply with respect to any information after two (2) years
    following the disclosure thereof or any information that the Receiving Party can
    document (a) is or becomes generally available to the public, or (b) was in its
    possession or known by it prior to receipt from the Disclosing Party, or (c) was
    rightfully disclosed to it without restriction by a third party, or (d) was
    independently developed without use of any Proprietary Information of the
    Disclosing Party or (e) is required to be disclosed by law.
24. AnimaApp shall own and retain all right, title and interest in and to (a) the
    Services and Resources, all improvements, enhancements or modifications
    thereto, (b) any software, applications, inventions or other technology developed
                                             5

    in connection with Implementation Resources or support, and (c) all intellectual
    property rights related to any of the foregoing.
25. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, AnimaApp shall have the right to
    collect and analyze data and other information relating to the provision, use and
    performance of various aspects of the Services and related systems and
    technologies (including, without limitation, information concerning Customer
    Data and data derived therefrom) and Company will be free (during and after
    the term hereof) to (i) use such information and data to improve and enhance
    the Services and for other development, diagnostic and corrective purposes in
    connection with the Services and other Company offerings, and (ii) disclose such
    data solely in aggregate or other de-identified form in connection with its
    business.
26. All content and resources created by you, including code you have generated
    with our software derived from your own design or free design samples, is yours
    forever, and we have no claims on it.
Beta Software and Early Access
27. You acknowledge that you know some of our Resources are in Beta version and
    that early access to such beta versions is granted for selected users only, you also
    acknowledge that the license to use our Resources (as provided by this
    Agreement) can be revoked by AnimaApp at any time. You further acknowledge
    that early access to a beta version does not imply free license to a non-beta
    version in future. You represent and warrant to keep the contents of the beta
    version CONFIDENTIAL AND PRIVATE.
Limitation of Warranties
28. Company shall use reasonable efforts consistent with prevailing industry
    standards to maintain the Services in a manner which minimizes errors and
    interruptions in the Services.
29. COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE;
    NOR DOES IT MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF
                                            6

    THE SERVICES.   ​EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS SECTION, THE SERVICES AND
    IMPLEMENTATION SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND COMPANY DISCLAIMS ALL
    WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
    MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
30. Furthermore, you understand and agree that:
   30.1.Any content downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of our
         Resources is done at your own discretion and risk, and that you are solely
         responsible for any damage to your computer or other devices for any loss
         of data that may result from the download of such content.
   30.2.No information or advice, whether expressed, implied, oral or written,
         obtained by you from AnimaApp or through any Resources we provide shall
         create any warranty, guarantee, or conditions of any kind, except for those
         expressly outlined in this User Agreement.
Limitation of Liability
31. In conjunction with the Limitation of Warranties as explained above, you
    expressly understand and agree that any claim against us shall be limited to the
    amount you paid, if any, for use of products and/or services during the 3 months
    preceding the above mentioned claims.
32. AnimaApp will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or
    exemplary loss or damages which may be incurred by you as a result of using our
    Resources, or as a result of any changes, data loss or corruption, cancellation,
    loss of access, or downtime to the full extent that applicable limitation of liability
    laws apply.
33. UNLESS OTHERWISE EXPRESSED, ANIMAAPP EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL
    WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,
    INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS
    OF    MERCHANTABILITY,       FITNESS    FOR    A   PARTICULAR       PURPOSE     AND
    NON-INFRINGEMENT.
                                            7

Copyrights/Trademarks
34. All content and materials available on AnimaApp, including but not limited to
    text, graphics, website name, subdomains, product names, code, images and
    logos (the "​Content​") are the intellectual property of AnimaApp (or of third
    parties which gave AnimaApp the right to use such materials and content), are
    protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
Termination of this Agreement
35. The company has the right to suspend or terminate this agreement in any time
    and without any notice.
36. Upon suspension or termination your right to use the Resources we provide will
    immediately cease.
37. You also have the right to cancel your account at any time without penalty.
38. In the event of account cancellation, either by you or us, you will lose all data
    related to your account that was stored on our servers. However, all content and
    resources created by you, including code you have generated with our software
    derived from your own design or free design samples, is yours forever, and we
    have no claims on it.
                                           8

                                     Privacy Policy
General
39. AnimaApp respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal
    information.
40. This privacy notice tells you the types of information we collect about you when
    you visit our sites ​animaapp.com​, ​animaapp.github.io​, ​fontbuddy.co​, its
    subdomains and other sites of ours (the “Site” or “Sites”) and use our products
    and services or which we otherwise obtain directly from you or from a third
    party, how we use that information, and the instances in which we share your
    information. This privacy notice may change from time to time so please check
    this policy regularly.
41. Our Site, products and services are not intended for children and we do not
    knowingly collect data relating to children.
42. AnimaApp is the controller and responsible for your personal information.
43. We have appointed a data privacy manager who is responsible for overseeing
    questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions about this
    privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact
    our data privacy manager by mailing privacy@animaapp.com, or using the details
    on the end of this document.
What Information We Collect
44. We collect two types of information regarding our Visitors and Users:
             44.1. Un-identified and non-identifiable information pertaining to a
         Visitor or un-identified User, which may be made available to us, or collected
         automatically via his/her use of the Services (“Non-personal Information”).
         Such Non-personal Information does not enable us to identify the Visitor or
         User from whom it was collected. The Non-personal Information collected
         by us mainly consists of technical and aggregated usage information, such as
         Visitors’ and Users’ browsing and ‘click-stream’ activity on the Services,
         session heatmaps and scrolls, non-identifying information regarding the
         Visitor’s or User’s device, operating system, internet browser, screen
                                            9

         resolution, language and keyboard settings, internet service provider,
         referring/exit pages, date/time stamps, etc.
             44.2. Individually identifiable information, namely information that
         identifies an individual or may with reasonable efforts cause the
         identification of an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature
         (“Personal Information” or “personal data”). The Personal Information
         collected by us mainly consists of contact details (e.g., e-mail address or
         phone number), billing details (name, physical billing address, payment
         method and transaction details), which are only collected from Users with
         Paid Services, details regarding a browsing or usage session (IP address,
         Geo-location and/or device unique identifier), details regarding connected
         third party accounts (such as the e-mail or username for a connected PayPal,
         Google or Facebook account), scanned identification documents provided to
         us (such as an ID card, driver’s license, passport or official company
         registration documents, student ID), correspondences (including those made
         through or uploaded to our Services), and any other Personal Information
         provided to us by Visitors and/or Users through their access to and/or use of
         the Services. For the avoidance of doubt, any Non-personal Information that
         is connected or linked to Personal Information (for example, in order to
         improve the Services we offer) is deemed and treated by us as Personal
         Information, as long as such connection or linkage exists.
45. Users of Users Information:
    We may also collect similar information pertaining to visitors and users of our
    User’s websites or services (“Users-of-Users”), solely for and on our Users’ behalf
    (as further described below).
How Do We Collect Such Information
46. We collect information through your use of the Services. When you visit or use
    our Services, including when you browse the Website or any User Website,
    register a User Account, edit your User Website and upload information and
    content, and/or download and use any of our plugins or other software. We are
                                           10

    aware of it and will usually gather, collect and record such uses, sessions and
    related information, either independently or with the help of third-party services
    as detailed below, including through the use of “cookies” and other tracking
    technologies, as further detailed below.
47. We collect information which you provide us voluntarily. For example, we collect
    the Personal Information you provide us when you register to our Services; when
    you sign in to our Services via third party services such as Facebook or Google;
    when you place purchases and/or subscribe to plans; when you submit or upload
    such Personal Information as you use any of our Services, websotes plugins, or
    other software; and/or when you contact us directly by any communication
    channel (e.g., AnimaApp’s support, emails, etc).
48. We also collect information from third party sources as described below.
Why Do We Collect Such Information
49. We collect such Non-personal and Personal Information for the following
    purposes:
              49.1. To provide and operate the Services.
              49.2. To further develop, customize and improve our Services, based
         on Visitors’ and Users’ common or personal preferences, experiences and
         difficulties.
              49.3. To provide our Users with ongoing customer assistance and
         technical support.
              49.4. To be able to contact our Visitors and Users with general or
         personalized service-related notices and promotional messages.
              49.5. To facilitate, sponsor and offer certain contests, events and
         promotions, determine participants’ eligibility, monitor performance,
         contact winners and grant prizes and benefits.
              49.6. To create aggregated statistical data and other aggregated and/or
         inferred Non-personal Information, which we or our business partners may
         use to provide and improve our respective services.
              49.7. To enhance our data security and fraud prevention capabilities
                                           11

              49.8. To consider Applicants’ candidacy for working at AnimaApp.
              49.9. To comply with any applicable laws and regulations.
50. We will only use your Personal Information for the purposes set out above where
    we are satisfied that:
              50.1. Our use of your Personal Information is necessary to perform a
          contract or take steps to enter into a contract with you (e.g. to provide you
          with a website builder, to provide you with our customer assistance and
          technical support), or
              50.2. Our use of your Personal Information is necessary to comply with
          a relevant legal or regulatory obligation that we have, or
              50.3. Our use of your Personal Information is necessary to support
          legitimate interests that we have as a business (for example, to maintain and
          improve our Services by identifying user trends and the effectiveness of
          AnimaApp’s campaigns and identifying technical issues), provided it is
          conducted at all times in a way that is proportionate, and that respects your
          privacy rights.
51. Our Services are not permitted to children under 18 years of age. No one under
    age 18 should provide any Personal Information to us through any of our
    Services. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under
    18. Parents and guardians should supervise their children's activities at all times.
Where Do We Store Your Information
52. AnimaApp Visitors’, AnimaApp Users’ and Users-of-Users’ Personal Information
    may be maintained, processed and stored by AnimaApp and our authorized
    affiliates and service providers in the United States of America, in Israel, and in
    other jurisdictions as necessary for the proper delivery of our Services and/or as
    may be required by law.
53. AnimaApp Jobs Applicants Information will be maintained, processed and stored
    in the United States of America, in Israel, in the applied position location(s), and
    as necessary, in secured cloud storage provided by our Third Party Services.
54. AnimaApp is based in Israel and in the state of New York, which are considered
                                             12

    by the European Commission to be offering an adequate level of protection for
    the Personal Information of EU Member State residents.
55. AnimaApp affiliates and service providers that store or process your Personal
    Information on AnimaApp’s behalf are each contractually committed to keep it
    protected and secured, in accordance with industry standards and regardless of
    any lesser legal requirements which may apply in their jurisdiction.
56. Data Localisation Obligations: If you reside in a jurisdiction that imposes “data
    localisation” or “data residency” obligations (i.e., requiring that Personal
    Information of its residents be kept within the territorial boundaries of such
    jurisdiction), and this fact comes to our attention, we may maintain your
    Personal Information within such territorial boundaries, if we are legally
    obligated to do so.
    You acknowledge that while doing so, we may continue to collect, store and use
    your Personal Information elsewhere, including in the United States of America
    as explained above.
Opting Out
57. Upon request AnimaApp will provide you with information about whether we
    hold any of your Personal Information. You may access, correct, or request
    deletion of your Personal Information by emailing to support@animaapp.com.
    We will respond to your request within a timeframe imposed by local laws or a
    reasonable timeframe.
58. Please note that permanently deleting your AnimaApp account erases all of your
    information from AnimaApp's databases. After completing this process, you can
    no longer use any of your AnimaApp Services, your User Account and all its data
    will be removed permanently, and AnimaApp will not be able to restore your
    account or retrieve your data in the future. If you contact AnimaApp Support in
    the future, the system will not recognize your account and Support agents will
    not be able to locate the deleted account.
                                          13

Users of Users
59. AnimaApp may collect, store and process certain Non-personal and Personal
    Information of Users-of-Users (“Users-of-Users Information”), solely on our
    Users’ behalf and at their direction. For example, each of our Users is able to
    import their e-mail contacts from third party services like Gmail, or otherwise
    collect and manage contacts via their User Website. Such contacts are then
    stored with AnimaApp, on the User’s behalf.
    For such purposes, AnimaApp serves and shall be considered as a “Processor”
    and not as the “Controller” (as both such capitalized terms are defined in the
    European Union General Data Protection Regulation) of such Users-of-Users
    Information. The Users controlling and operating such User Websites shall be
    considered as the “Controllers” of such Users-of-Users Information, and are
    responsible for complying with all laws and regulations that may apply to the
    collection and control of such Users-of-Users Information, including all privacy
    and data protection laws of all relevant jurisdictions.
    You are responsible for the security, integrity and authorized usage of your
    Users-of-Users’ Personal Information, and for obtaining consents, permissions
    and providing any fair processing notices required for the collection and usage of
    such information.
    AnimaApp cannot provide legal advice to Users or their Users-of-Users, however
    we do recommend that all Users publish and maintain clear and comprehensive
    privacy policies on their User Websites, in accordance with the applicable laws
    and regulations, and that all Users-of-Users carefully read those policies and
    make sure that they consent to them.
    If you are a visitor, user or customer of any of our Users, please read the
    following: AnimaApp has no direct relationship with the individual Users-of-Users
    whose Personal Information it processes. If you are a visitor, user or customer of
    any of our Users, and would like to make any requests or queries regarding your
    Personal Information, please contact such User(s) directly. For example, if you
    wish to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate information processed by
    AnimaApp on behalf of its Users, please direct your query to the relevant User
                                           14

    (who is the “Controller” of such data). If requested to remove any
    Users-of-Users’ Personal Information, we will respond to such request within
    thirty (30) days. Unless otherwise instructed by our User, we will retain their
    Users-of-Users’ Personal Information until revoked by them.
Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties
AnimaApp may share your Personal Information with third parties (or otherwise
allow them access to it) only in the following manners and instances:
60. Third Party Services:
    AnimaApp has partnered with a number of selected service providers, whose
    services and solutions complement, facilitate and enhance our own. These
    include hosting and server co-location services, communications and content
    delivery networks (CDNs), data and cyber security services, billing and payment
    processing services, domain name registrars, fraud detection and prevention
    services, web analytics, e-mail distribution and monitoring services, session
    recording and remote access services, performance measurement, data
    optimization and marketing services, content providers, and our legal and
    financial advisors (collectively, “Third Party Service(s)”).
    Such Third Party Services may receive or otherwise have access to our Visitors’
    and Users’ Personal Information and/or Users-of-Users’ Personal Information, in
    its entirety or in part – depending on each of their particular roles and purposes
    in facilitating and enhancing our Services and business, and may only use it for
    such purposes.
    Note that while our Services may contain links to other websites or services, we
    are not responsible for such websites’ or services’ privacy practices. We
    encourage you to be aware when you leave our Services and read the privacy
    statements of each and every website and service you visit before providing your
    Personal Information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such linked third
    -party websites and services.
                                             15

61. Law Enforcement, Legal Requests and Duties:
    Where permitted by local data protection laws, AnimaApp may disclose or
    otherwise allow others access to your Personal Information pursuant to a legal
    request, such as a subpoena, legal proceedings, search warrant or court order, or
    in compliance with applicable laws, if we have good faith belief that the law
    requires us to do so, with or without notice to you.
62. Protecting Rights and Safety:
    AnimaApp may share your Personal Information with others if we believe in good
    faith that this will help protect the rights, property or personal safety of
    AnimaApp, any of our Users, any Users-of-Users, or any member of the general
    public, with or without notice to you.
63. Social Media Features and Framed Pages:
    Our Services include certain Social Media features and widgets, single sign on
    features, such as the “Facebook Connect” or “Google Sign-in”, the “Facebook
    Like” button, the “Share this” button or other interactive mini-programs (“Social
    Media Features”).These Social Media Features may collect information such as
    your IP address or which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a
    cookie to enable them to function properly. Social Media Features are either
    hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with
    these third parties’ Social Media Features are governed by their policies and not
    ours.
    In addition, our Services may enable you to share your Personal Information with
    third parties directly, such as via page framing techniques to serve content to or
    from Third Party Services or other parties, while preserving the look and feel of
    our Website and Services (“Frames”). Please be aware that if you choose to
    interact or share any Personal Information via such Frames, you are in fact
    providing it to these third parties and not to us, and such interactions and
    sharing too are governed by such third parties’ policies and not ours.
64. AnimaApp Subsidiaries and Affiliated Companies:
    We may share Personal Information internally within our family of companies,
    for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share your
                                           16

    Personal Information with AnimaApp, our US-based subsidiary, in the course of
    facilitating and providing you (and your Users-of-Users) with our Services. In
    addition, should AnimaApp or any of its affiliates undergo any change in control,
    including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of substantially all of its
    assets, your Personal Information may be shared with the parties involved in
    such event. If we have good faith that such change in control might materially
    affect your Personal Information stored with us, we will notify you via e-mail
    and/or prominent notice on our Website of this event and certain choices you
    may have regarding your Personal Information.
65. To clarify, AnimaApp may share your Personal Information in manners other than
    as described above, pursuant to your explicit approval, or if we are legally
    obligated to do so. Moreover, AnimaApp may transfer, share, disclose or
    otherwise use Non-personal Information in its sole discretion and without the
    need for further approval.
Cookies Policy
66. Our Sites uses cookies and similar technologies to distinguish you from other
    users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you
    browse our Site and allows us to improve our Site. We may also use such
    technologies to track you across the Internet and to display targeted
    advertisements to you on our Site and third party websites and social media
    platforms based on your preferences and likely interests.
67. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or
    the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is
    transferred to your computer's hard drive.
68. The types of cookies we use on our Site are:
              68.1. Strictly Necessary Cookies. We use Strictly Necessary Cookies to
          operate our Site. These cookies are essential to enable you to move around
          the Site, use its features and to log into secure areas of the Site.
              68.2. Functionality Cookies. We use Functionality Cookies to recognise
          you when you return to our Site. This enables us to personalise our content
                                              17

         for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences and various
         settings on our Site
             68.3. Analytical/Performance       Cookies.    These    cookies    collect
         information about how many people are using our Site and how they are
         moving around it when they re using it. For example, the pages visited most
         often, how people are moving from one link to another, and if they get error
         messages from certain pages. This helps us to improve the way our Site
         works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking
         for easily.
             68.4. Targeting     Cookies.   These   cookies   are   used to deliver
         advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests. They
         remember that you have visited our website, the pages you visited and the
         links you have followed. This information may be shared with other
         organisations such as our advertising partners.
69. Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and
    providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use
    cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be
    Analytical/Performance Cookies or Targeting Cookies.
70. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you
    when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note
    that some parts of this Site may become inaccessible or not function properly.
Communications from AnimaApp
71. Promotional Messages:
    We may use your Personal Information to send you promotional content and
    messages by e-mail, text messages, direct text messages, marketing calls and
    similar forms of communication from AnimaApp or our partners (acting on
    AnimaApp’s behalf) through such means.
    If you do not wish to receive such promotional messages or calls, you may notify
    us at any time or follow the “unsubscribe” instructions contained in the
    promotional communications you receive.
                                           18

    We take steps to limit the promotional content we send you to a reasonable and
    proportionate level, and to send you information which we believe may be of
    interest or relevance to you, based on your information.
72. Service and Billing Messages:
    AnimaApp may also contact you with important information regarding our
    Services, or your use thereof.
    For example, we may send you a notice (through any of the means available to
    us) if a certain Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance; reply to your
    support ticket or e-mail; send you reminders or warnings regarding upcoming or
    late payments for your current or upcoming subscriptions; forward abuse
    complaints regarding your User Website; or notify you of material changes in our
    Services.
    It is important that you are always able to receive such messages. For this
    reason, you are not be able to opt-out of receiving such Service and Billing
    Messages unless you are no longer a AnimaApp Visitor or User (which can be
    done by deactivating your account).
Data Retention
73. We may retain your Personal Information (as well as your Users-of-Users’
    Information) for as long as your User Account is active, as indicated in this
    Privacy Policy or as otherwise needed to provide you with our Services.
    We may continue to retain such Personal Information even after you deactivate
    your User Account and/or cease to use any particular Services, as reasonably
    necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes regarding our
    Users or their Users-of-Users, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our agreements
    and/or protect our legitimate interests.
    We maintain a data retention policy which we apply to information in our care.
    Where your Personal Information is no longer required we will ensure it is
    securely deleted.
Security
                                           19

74. AnimaApp has implemented security measures designed to protect the Personal
    Information you share with us, including physical, electronic and procedural
    measures. Among other things, we offer HTTPS secure access to most areas on
    our Services; the transmission of sensitive payment information (such as a credit
    card number) through our designated purchase forms is protected by an industry
    standard SSL/TLS encrypted connection; and we regularly maintain a PCI DSS
    (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards) certification. We also regularly
    monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, and regularly seek
    new ways and Third Party Services for further enhancing the security of our
    Services and protection of our Visitors’ and Users’ privacy.
    Regardless of the measures and efforts taken by AnimaApp, we cannot and do
    not guarantee the absolute protection and security of your Personal Information,
    your Users-of-Users’ Information or any other User Content you upload, publish
    or otherwise share with AnimaApp or anyone else.
    We therefore encourage you to set strong passwords for your User Account and
    User Website, and avoid providing us or anyone with any sensitive information of
    which you believe its disclosure could cause you substantial or irreparable harm.
    Furthermore, because certain areas on our Services are less secure than others
    (for example, if you set your Support forum ticket to be “Public” instead of
    “Private”, or if you browse to a non-SSL page), and since e-mail and instant
    messaging are not recognized as secure forms of communications, we request
    and encourage you not to share any Personal Information on any of these areas
    or via any of these methods.
    If you have any questions regarding the security of our Services, you are welcome
    to contact us at ​privacy@animaapp.com​.
Public Forums and User Content
75. Our Services offer publicly accessible websites, blogs, communities and support
    forums. Please be aware that any information you provide in any such areas may
    be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of
    your Personal Information from our blogs, communities or forums, feel free to
    contact us at: privacy@animaapp.com. In some cases, we may not be able to
                                           20

    remove your Personal Information from such areas. For example, if you use a
    third party application to post a comment (e.g., the Facebook social plugin
    application) while logged in to your related profile with such third party, you
    must login into such application or contact its provider if you want to remove the
    Personal Information you posted on that platform.
76. In any event, we advise against posting any information (or use any posting
    means to post information) you don’t wish to publicize on these platforms.
77. If you upload any User Content to your User Account or post it on your User
    Website and/or provide it in any other way as part of the use of any Service, you
    do so at your own risk.
78. We have put adequate security measures in place to protect your Personal
    Information. However, we cannot control the actions of other Users or members
    of the public who may access your User Content, and are not responsible for the
    circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures you or we may have
    placed on your User Website (including, for instance, password-protected areas
    on your User Website). You understand and acknowledge that, even after its
    removal by you or us, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and
    archived pages or if any third parties (including any of your Users-of-Users) have
    copied or stored such User Content. To clarify, we advise against uploading or
    posting any information you do not wish to be public
Updates and Interpretation
79. We may update this Privacy Policy as required by applicable law, and to reflect
    changes to our information collection, usage and storage practices. We
    encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our
    privacy practices.
80. Unless stated otherwise, our most current Privacy Policy applies to all
    information that we have about you and your Users-of-Users, with respect to our
    Websites, AnimaApp Apps, Mobile Apps, plugins and other Services.
                                           21

81. Any heading, caption or section title contained herein, is provided only for
    convenience, and in no way defines or explains any section or provision hereof,
    or legally binds any of us in any way.
82. This Privacy Policy was written in English, and may be translated into other
    languages for your convenience. If a translated (non-English) version of this
    Privacy Policy conflicts in any way with its English version, the provisions of the
    English version shall prevail.
Miscellaneous
83. If any provision of this Agreement is found to be unenforceable or invalid, that
    provision will be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that
    this Agreement will otherwise remain in full force and effect and enforceable.
84. This Agreement is the complete and exclusive statement of the mutual
    understanding of the parties and supersedes and cancels all previous written and
    oral agreements, communications and other understandings relating to the
    subject matter of this Agreement, and that all waivers and modifications must be
    in a writing signed by both parties, except as otherwise provided herein.
85. No agency, partnership, joint venture, or employment is created as a result of
    this Agreement and Customer does not have any authority of any kind to bind
    Company in any respect whatsoever.
86. It is agreed that the Company may present the customer as its client, both in the
    company's website and other promotional publications including press release.
87. In any action or proceeding to enforce rights under this Agreement, the
    prevailing party will be entitled to recover costs and attorneys' fees.
88. Company may transfer and assign any of its rights and obligations under this
    Agreement without consent.
89. This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of Delaware without
    regard to its conflict of laws provisions. Both parties further consent to the
    personal jurisdiction of and exclusive venue in competent courts in Delaware,
    Delaware, as the legal forum for any dispute between them.
                                            22

90. If any part of this Agreement is held invalid or unenforceable, the remaining
    provisions of it will remain in full effect and an enforceable term will be
    substituted reflecting yours and our intent as closely as possible. Either party’s
    failure to enforce any term or condition in this Agreement is not a waiver of its
    right to do so later.
91. All sections of this Agreement which by their nature should survive termination
    will survive termination, including, without limitation, accrued rights to payment,
    confidentiality obligations, warranty disclaimers, and limitations of liability.
Contacting Us
Email:          support@AnimaApp.com
Phone:          +1 347-674-6327
Postal:         Anima App, Inc.
                2035 Sunset Lake Road Suite B-2
                Newark, DE 19702
Last Update
This version was last updated on 23rd May 2018.
                                           23
